It's like a bad horror movie, only worse.
Dead & Breakfast is a horror, comedy, music film directed by Matthew Leutwyler.
Six friends on a road trip stop for the night at a bed and
breakfast in the sleepy town of Lovelock.
After a night that leaves both the inn's owner and chef dead, the gang
finds themselves under suspicion by the local sheriff.
But that's only the beginning as nearly all of the town's quirky residents become
possessed by an evil spirit and pin down the friends inside the B&B.
Christian, played by Jeremy Sisto.
David, played by Erik Palladino.
Kate, played by Bianca Lawson.
Johnny, played by Osgood Perkins.
Sara, played by Ever Carradine.
Melody, played by Gina Philips.
Dead & Breakfast is a 2004 musical zombie comedy film  directed by Matthew Leutwyler starring Ever
Carradine, Gina Philips, Erik Palladino, Bianca Lawson, Jeremy Sisto and Oz Perkins.
The film premiered at the South by Southwest Film Festival
and went on to win over a dozen awards.
It was also nominated for a Saturn Award.
The film explores themes of gore, bed and breakfast (b&b), zombie.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.